<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>
    <string name="activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="tab_cafe">cafe</string>
    <string name="tab_fastFood">fast food</string>
    <string name="tab_arabic">arabic</string>
    <string name="Mama_Jamila_Cafe">Mama Jamila Cafe</string>
    <string name="Mama_Jamila_about">Group of Saudi young people with many new items in the food menu . Juices made from fresh fruit and they have special coffee for coffee freaks. You can find Belgian waffle ( made from scratch, Original Recipe ) and English Muffin as well. Amazing decoration inside worth watching.
The staff are very kind.</string>
    <string name="Strawberry_and_Cheese">Strawberry and Cheese</string>
    <string name="Strawberry_and_Cheese_about">Homemade cheesecake since 1999 by Eman Dahlawi.\n Cheesecake Toppings: Strawberry, Blueberry, Mango, Pineapple, Caramel, Chocolate, Coffee, Marshmallow and Apple Caramel with Cinnamon.\n Call us and order from our delicious mouthwatering cheesecakes and come to pick it up. If you have any suggestions please feel free to contact us.</string>
    <string name="Zamzam_Lobby_Lounge">Zamzam Lobby Lounge</string>
    <string name="Zamzam_Lobby_Lounge_about">Pullman ZamZam Makkah stands as a distinctive landmark in Makkah, located in the spectacular new Abraj Al Bait complex, directly adjoining Masjid Al Haram and the holy Kaaba in the very heart of Makkah facing King Abdulaziz gate. This masterpiece offers the finest hospitality in Makkah, having 1315 elegantly appointed rooms and suites with extravagant amenities, two contemporary dining options and five-star-deluxe services filled with spirituality while enjoying direct views over the holy Kaaba.</string>
    <string name="Burger_King">Burger King</string>
    <string name="Burger_King_about">Every day, more than 11 million guests visit BURGER KING® restaurants around the world. And they do so because our restaurants are known for serving high-quality, great-tasting, and affordable food. Founded in 1954, BURGER KING® is the second largest fast food hamburger chain in the world. The original HOME OF THE WHOPPER®, our commitment to premium ingredients, signature recipes, and family-friendly dining experiences is what has defined our brand for more than 50 successful years.</string>
    <string name="pizza_hut">Pizza Hut</string>
    <string name="pizza_hut_about">The Pizza Hut story begins in May 1958. Dan and Frank Carney opened their 550 squarefoot pizza restaurant in Wichita, Kansas. Dan and Frank, with friends Richard Beemer and John Bender, made the pizza themselves. Frank rolled the dough with a rolling pin. Richard tossed the dough in the air from the pie tin. Dan filled the unbaked crust with sauce. John flipped the pie from the tin during the baking process. Dan Carney recalled, The people were enchanted with the product, watching us tossing the dough over our heads. They were really enjoying themselves…. The Carneys created an innovative, high quality, engaging, informal eating experience in a friendly neighborhood restaurant. Pizza Hut became a popular place with the teenage and college crowd. Pizza Hut attracted families that enjoyed a night out eating a meal that they would not be having at home. After the families left, Pizza Hut transformed itself into a hangout for college age kids. Having a good time was an essential part of Pizza Hut. The idea caught on. A second Pizza Hut opened in December 1958 in downtown Wichita. By 1963, there were 42 Pizza Hut restaurants.\nPizza Hut was always an entrepreneurial, innovative, fast-thinking place. It was the kind of organization where everyone shared the learning. As Frank Carney said, To me, the biggest strength of Pizza Hut was that we had an awful lot of people who came up with great ideas.</string>
    <string name="Al_Tazaj">Al Tazaj</string>
    <string name="Al_Tazaj_about">Many commercial, cultural and investment ideas are bred in the the environment we live in. If these ideas do not blossom from the basis and understanding that one envisions for one\'s self, then these ideas blossom in a tight and narrow space;whether written on paper, studied and implemented. If that is the case, then one is doomed to a limited and narrow experience.\nWE DO NOT COMPETE WITH WHAT ALREADY IS OR IMITATE WHAT WAS ALREADY DONE\nWith this understanding, the first “Al Tazaj” restaurant opened in the Holy City of Mecca in 1989 in Al Aziziyah Main Road. The initial idea behind this endeavor was to sell small chicken (Aged 23 days) fresh from Al Fakih Poultry Farm.\nIn addition, the chickens used were marinated in a natural blend of garlic, tomato,lemon,ginger and spices and are barbecued on coal. Therefore, we have no secret recipe! With all thanks to God, the Al Tazaj franchise grew and spread to cover the region of the middle east with more  </string>
    <string name="al_Kawthar_Lounge">Al Kawthar Lounge</string>
    <string name="al_Kawthar_Lounge_about">Boasting a prime location and fabulous views of the Haram and Kaaba, Conrad Makkah offers contemporary luxury and warm, authentic hospitality in the heart of the Holy City of Makkah.\nOur hotel received the TripAdvisor Certificate of Excellence in 2017.</string>
    <string name="al_Khairat">AL Khairat</string>
    <string name="al_Khairat_about">Our authentic and exquisite restaurant offers a wide variety of international and oriental cuisines. Delicious feast in the distinguished ambience of Al Khairat enhances memorable gatherings of families and friends.\nOur restaurant offers prime dining that is firmly set upon the delights of the palate. From the international specialties to Arabian favourites Al Khairat provides mouth-watering delicacies to please every diner, as well as the atmosphere of comfort, relaxation, and peacefulness.</string>
    <string name="al_Atbaq">Al Atbaq</string>
    <string name="al_Atbaq_about">A one stop restaurant for CHINESE / ARABIC / PAKISTANI and INDIAN food.\nWe are not fast food but we serve FRESH food fast!\n An amazing restaurant, For over three decades Al Atbaq has been the benchmark by which other restaurants are measured. A Mecca landmark at Hussain Arab Street, Al Atbaq has been home to the great and the good. Juxtaposed between the bustling metropolitan areas of Al Haram and Siteen, which abound with luxury hotels, boutiques, art galleries and iconic attractions, Al Atbaq provides the ultimate destination to enjoy the quintessential Mecca experience.</string>
    <string name="img_description">photo</string>
    <string name="txt_about">about</string>
    <string name="hotel_Pullman_ZamZam">Pullman ZamZam</string>
    <string name="hotel_Pullman_ZamZam_about">ZamZam Pullman Makkah stands as a distinctive landmark in Makkah, located in the spectacular new Abraj Al Bait complex, directly adjoining Masjid Al Haram and the holy Kaaba in the very heart of Makkah facing King Abdulaziz gate. This masterpiece offers the finest hospitality in Makkah, having 1315 elegantly appointed rooms and suites with extravagant amenities, two contemporary dining options and five-star-deluxe services filled with spirituality while enjoying direct views over the holy Kaaba.</string>
    <string name="hotel_Jabal_Omar_Hyatt_Regency">Hyatt Regency</string>
    <string name="hotel_Jabal_Omar_Hyatt_Regency_about">Discover All That Hyatt\'s Luxurious Makkah Hotel Has to Offer Situated at the heart of the holy city of Makkah, Jabal Omar Hyatt Regency Makkah offers visitors and pilgrims alike a unique hospitality experience, blending comfort and convenience in an elegant atmosphere. The hotel is just a one-minute walk to Al-Masjid Al-Haram. It is readily accessible by road, with seamless connectivity to and from Jeddah, the region’s urban center and main port city, as well as King Abdulaziz International Airport. What Makes a Seamless Stay: Modern rooms: 656 spacious guestrooms and suites, feature plush Hyatt Grand Beds™ as well as panoramic views of the holy city Best location in the holy city: For your comfort, an ideal location just one-minute walk to Al-Masjid Al-Haram Inspired dining: Enjoy a wide range of dining experiences at our on-site-restaurants or get together with your beloved ones in the Tea Lounge Ample amenities: Stay connected with complimentary Wi-Fi, work out in the 24-hour fitness centre, and more</string>
    <string name="hotel_Jabal_Omar_Marriott">Jabal Omar Marriott</string>
    <string name="hotel_Jabal_Omar_Marriott_about">Conveniently located in the heart of the holy city of Makkah, within Jabal Omar complex development, Jabal Omar Marriott Hotel is few minute’s walk ( 500 steps ) close to Haram, Kaaba. Although the hotel is steps away from Haram, free shuttle service is offer to elderly and special needs guests. The hotel is also close to many of Makkah\'s prestigious Holy sites. This five-star hotel in Makkah, Saudi Arabia offers 426 contemporary, spacious guest rooms including 52 suites, an opulent and inviting lobby and reception area. Our hotel features two restaurants Spice Market and Olive both offering views of the city and the Holy Haram in addition to Atrium Café serves pastries and soft drinks. These versatile dining venues offer a creative and extensive array of international and local specialties. Fully equipped business center with secretarial service, 5 medium size meeting rooms with a large pre-function area are available.</string>
    <string name="hotel_Hilton">Hilton</string>
    <string name="hotel_Hilton_about">A landmark hotel in Makkah and only moments away from the Haram, Hilton Makkah Convention Hotel offers majestic views of the Haram and is steps away from the Holy Kaaba. The hotel features 764 rooms and suites with breathtaking views of the city and the Haram, 3 restaurants, 2 Lounges, a fitness center, a 24-hour business center, 8 meeting rooms and boasts the largest pillar free ballroom in town.</string>
    <string name="Kaaba">Kaaba</string>
    <string name="Jabal_al_Nour">Jabal al-Nour</string>
    <string name="Jabal_al_Nour_about">Jabal an-Nour is a mountain near Mecca in the Hejazi region of Saudi Arabia. The mountain houses the famed Grotto/Cave of Hira (Arabic: غَـار حِـرَاء‎, romanized: Ġār Ḥirāʾ). The mountain and its cave hold tremendous significance for Muslims throughout the world, as the Islamic Nabī (Prophet) Muhammad is said to have spent a great deal of time in the cave meditating, and it is widely believed that it was here that he received his first revelation, which consisted of the first five ayats of Surah Al-Alaq from the angel Jibrā’īl . It is one of the most popular tourist attractions in Makkah. The mountain itself is barely 640 m (2,100 ft) tall; nonetheless one to two hours are needed to make the strenuous hike to the cave. Its 1750 steps to the top, which can take anywhere between 25minutes to 1hr 30 minutes.</string>
    <string name="Abraj_Al_Bait_Towers">Abraj Al-Bait Towers</string>
    <string name="Abraj_Al_Bait_Towers_about">The Abraj Al-Bait is a government-owned megatall complex of seven skyscraper hotels in Mecca, Saudi Arabia. These towers are a part of the King Abdulaziz Endowment Project that strives to modernize the city in catering to its pilgrims. The central hotel tower, the Makkah Royal Clock Tower, A Fairmont Hotel, has the world\'s largest clock face and is the third-tallest building and fifth-tallest freestanding structure in the world.\nThe building complex is metres away from the world\'s largest mosque and Islam\'s most sacred site, the Great Mosque of Mecca. The developer and contractor of the complex is the Saudi Binladin Group, the Kingdom\'s largest construction company. It is the world\'s most expensive building with the total cost of construction equaling US$15 billion. The complex was built after the demolition of the Ajyad Fortress, the 18th-century Ottoman citadel on top of a hill overlooking the Grand Mosque. The destruction of the historically significant site in 2002 by the Saudi government sparked international outcry and a strong response from Turkey.</string>
    <string name="Kaaba_about">The Kaaba also referred to as al-Kaʿbah al-Musharrafah (Arabic: ٱلْكَعْبَة ٱلْمُشَرَّفَة‎, the Holy Ka\'bah), is a building at the center of Islam\s most important mosque, Al-Masjid Al-Ḥarām (Arabic: أَلمَسْجِد أَلحَرَام‎, The Sacred Mosque), in the Hejazi city of Mecca, Saudi Arabia.It is the most sacred site in Islam. It is considered by Muslims to be the Bayt Allāh (Arabic: بَيْت الله‎, "House of God"). Its location determines the qiblah (Arabic: قِبْلَة‎, direction of prayer). Wherever they are in the world, Muslims are expected to face the Kaaba when performing Salah the Islamic prayer.</string>
</resources>

